If you hate AI, this video is for you.
Because the bad news is it will take
parts of your job. While half of the
internet is still arguing about whether
AI should even be allowed to exist, the
people using it every day already know
this is the most powerful piece of
technology in our lifetime. We are using
it every day and most of the people
screaming about it or not. Most anti-AII
opinions are still coming from people
reacting to slop, theft, anxiety, and
culture war aesthetics without ever
spending serious time inside cloud
codecs or modern agent workflows. They
are not wrong about the garbage. They
are wrong about the trajectory. The
point of view is emotional first,
aesthetic first, moral first. It is not
utilitarian, and it's not grounded in
what these tools now do in the hands of
the people who actually use them like
us. And you can riot against it if you
want and it is still going to happen and
we are going to show you why.
>> What did you do this week with like all
of the prompts
>> I'm doing a lot with it. I think I don't
know if my customers are watching and I
tell them but I didn't touch any code at
all this year. If it's a PP Laravel
project, if it's building WordPress, if
it's Python,
>> yeah,
>> everything I put in and I have some some
flows that check each other like Codex
Cloud, but yeah, the code is still
better than what I would do before. And
it's so much faster. Even the the most
easiest thing like a WordPress website,
people would install so many plugins,
buy them for like $50 a year, and you
have a whole list. And now customers
come to me because the website is slow
and cloud just rebuilds all the plugins
to custom plugins within an hour and it
optimizes the website. So for example
like do you think like security
engineers will like scream against
methos because it's too powerful and
they don't have anything to do
>> Oh yeah I think for two reasons because
the first reason is they are losing
their jobs and the second reason is they
know how fast it can go because they
know how security works and once you
bypass a small thing they understand how
easy it is to leak a full database of
data.
>> Yeah. So they are the ones saying that
when MTOS is leaked into the wrong hands
of people abusing it, using it for bad
behavior, for hacking and everything.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, who's going to stop them?
>> Who's going to stop? Anyone?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Mitos was a bit like that was
honestly during our live stream when I
saw like the benchmark and stuff, I was
okay, that's that's the ponder box. The
guy who said, "Yeah, okay. I found a bug
in a 30 years old code is like OpenBSD
server and I can be admin on every
[__] OpenBSD ever on Earth, bro.
>> Yeah, but it's not even in your code.
Just the the operating system that's
running on a VPS or whatever, everything
can be hacked. And then even if your app
is fully secure, you still have a
problem.
>> You're never fully secure anyway, right?
And and then you we will have MTOS 1.5
and MTOS 2.0.
>> Yeah. And what are you going to tell
your customer every time? Oh no, it's
AI. I can do anything about it.
>> I mean like the solution of AI attacks
or AI defenders. AI prompting is not
art. Like do you understand the
backlash?
>> Yeah. They say they trained on my data
on my on my art and now it's using my
techniques to create new art for other
people.
>> Yeah. Fantasy artist Greg Rutoski image
was scrapped the most out of the any
artist across all generative AI site.
Rutoski was not happy and made vocal
opposition of AI generated art. As a
result, his art was removed from
training data set of the diffusion 2.0.
However, Gen AI user developed tools
like Laura to bypass the new stable
diffusion restriction. The net is is now
filled with AI rtosk ripoff and kind of
like what we saw with the studio Gibli
with JGBT, right?
>> Yes. you put limitation in a closed
model, then you will have open-source
models that will do exactly the same
[__] thing. So, it's that's it. It's
open. And I mean, yeah, that looks like
an illustration that you can prompt on
Nano2 like in 5 seconds.
>> I would just say you're an artist. Be
creative and turn it around and make
money on it. tell people that's based on
your art and they can can even get an
original one.
>> Exactly.
>> Eventually AI will steal it and not even
steal it, it will just copy it, create
something. But even if it does it by
itself and it goes through the same
steps as you have done, it will come to
the same result. That's possible. So
don't complain. Just go and earn money
with AI because of so many opportunities
that you get. Be creative and use AI to
go even further.
>> Yeah. And I like Yeah. People can sell
like humanmade art anyway. You will have
you will have like 1 million piece of AI
art and then you will have one painting
where you spend 20,000 hours on it
>> and people will pay for it. There's no
because they want the personal stuff.
>> People are saying, "Yeah, we need a
label. We need to force people tagging
if it's AI generated."
>> Yeah.
>> When 70% of the content on internet is
AI generated. Like what the [__] are you
talking about? Yeah. And they are not
going to do it.
>> I mean on YouTube like if the video is
AI generated you need to tag it and on
on Instagram too like if the like the
some of the AI influencer I have on
Instagram I need to say that the image
is AI generated and then I get like some
DM from fan view
influencers that say oh yeah you want to
create an account here. Okay.
>> Yeah it's an upsell.
>> Yeah. A girl on Instagram with like big
boobs and like bikinis will make more
views than ugly real girl.
>> Yeah. And I don't think people mind that
it's AI. They just keep on scrolling.
>> I mean when you when you see the the the
impression of those like AI generated
models. No, people don't give a [__]
about
>> all of the view that we get right now is
because YouTube algo recommended to the
viewers, right? So we produce the
content, it get recommended to people.
We could AI generated everything and
YouTube could recommen recommend like
content not even human generated or
generate a video to get the viewers to
watch a video about a search or you can
search something on YouTube and the
video that you want to watch is
generated on the fly.
>> Yeah, that's cool.
>> Yeah,
>> but that's like giving everybody a
unique video. Yeah, but like for examp
like like for example if I want to watch
a cooking video on YouTube like I say
which recipe can I do with my fridge?
Like the the stuff I have in my fridge.
You take a picture of your fridge, you
go on YouTube, bam video of like cooking
something recipe blah blah blah in like
it's so exciting. AI is like 100% too
big to fail. It's not because you will
have like riot in France or whatever
like 15,000
people like rioting. Yeah, know we don't
want self-driving cars or we don't want
AI generated images on internet. We're
going to make billion of them. So,
>> you better get used to it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Get used to it before like
your kids are scrolling TikTok with AI
generated content.
>> Yeah. Well, maybe it's a generation
issue.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> In 30 years, no, we are the last people
knowing how everything works without AI.
>> Yeah. Oh, like when kids are like
getting brain rotated on Tik Tok by like
the banana fruit stuff generated like
yeah in in yeah in 10 years nobody will
care about like if it's AI because
everything will be generated anyways.
>> Yes.
>> But yeah you can riot you can hate AI
but you're gonna lose. I subscribe to
the channel.
>> Thank you. Bye and stream. Peace.